Please contact turkision@gmail.com for any inquiries
No living being was harmed
during the filming of this series.
Episode 107
You can't escape from my grasp.
My Allah, help us.
Alps, prepare defense measures with fire.
Wait for my order!
Do it now!
Don't leave any of them alive.
Oh right!
Your punishment will be worse than this.
We demolished their headquarters, Olof.
We have to go.
This is just the beginning.
They will pay for every
drop of blood they shed.
We'll make them pay, Olof.
We'll do it together.
But not now,
not now.
We will back off.
What is this headquarters, Osman Bey?
From whom did you obtain permission
to establish a headquarters?
From Allah.
I do not take permission from
anyone to fight for the truth.
If you don't know me...
ask who is next to you.
He knows me well.
You are wronging me, Osman Bey.
I totally give you your right.
Avcı Bey.
Go to the headquarters
with our soldiers.
Help those who have been hurt for the
sake of those who see daydreaming.
No.
We don't need anyone's help.
You spoil the reconciliation
between the two countries.
And on top of that, you get raided.
You will pay for it.
We pay the price no matter what.
Whenever you want and wherever you want.
Turgut Bey.
You stay.
He is going, my Sultan.
What if he arrives early?
He hardly reaches there in the morning.
Upon arrival...
Everyone will be dead.
There you see, right?
What, Sultan?
Osman's arrogance.
His arrogance will defeat himself.
You have to choose your side now.
Are you next to Osman or next to me?
Yenişehir
It is not found anywhere.
The warriors at the door don't
know anything.
He left Yenişehir in the morning.
He did not come back.
Something must have happened to him.
Yes.
Say good things, Ayşe Hatun.
Perhaps he fled to the tribe.
No, Ulgen.
Bengi's daughter had run away, would
she have stood still?
She would already raid the palace.
There she is.
Look.
Speak of the devil.
The woman whose daughter ran away,
would she come to the market?
There is something wrong with it.
Appear before me if you dare.
I will know who you are.
Stand before me, you coward dog.
Subasi.
It's your turn.
Torture him well.
Don't worry.
Well.
Let's go to Yenişehir.
They may suspect us if they don't see us.
I am a man who recently got engaged.
I'll go and mind my bu.siness.
Come on.
Take this.
Didn't they run away?
Woe to us!
If Alçiçek is here...
where is Aktemur?
Come, Ülgen, let's find out
something from this girl.
Come on.
Ayşe Hatun.
Ülgen Hatun.
What do you want from me?
- Alçiçek, Aktemur...
- My mother is coming.
I don't want her to see you.
Don't mention that name to me again.
That matter is over.
What are you saying, Alçiçek?
I will marry Bayındır Bey.
Get away from me.
Walk.
I did not understand anything.
what is happening?
It is clear that Alçiçek
changed her mind.
Oh, Aktemur.
I've decided to go out
on my way, mother.
Or you are...?
I will kidnap Alçiçek.
Did you offer to run away?
She offered it.
When we leave the castle...
She is a brave girl.
Since she loves you so much that
she leaves her parents...
Don't worry.
Go do what you must.
I stand behind you.
I won't make her wait, she's waiting for
me near the compound of pines.
Let your path be open.
Be careful, Aktemur.
Sisters!
Aktemur is lost.
Inform Malhun Hatun immediately.
We're going to the place
Aktemur mentioned.
Come on, warriors.
Prepare the horses, we're going.
I will come with you too.
I won't leave you alone.
Come, Ülgen.
Alps.
We'll get out quickly.
We will bury our martyrs in Yenişehir.
Osman Bey is coming.
Catapults.
We put a lot of effort into making it.
We made a lot of effort.
Are you well?
I'm good.
Bala.
My Bala.
My brave wife.
Are you well?
I'm fine, Osman.
But...
They completely destroyed the place.
Oh.
Alps.
Is this you how you trust your Bey?
Is it?
Come here.
They attacked our headquarters
when we turned our backs.
Get out!
I stand behind you all these years.
Your anger blinded your eyes, Osman Bey.
You kick me out at my first mistake.
Turgut Bey is right.
Go away!
Boran.
Summon the Beys.
I will hold the court.
Your command, my Bey.
They broke our arm.
But we will not stop.
They want to
cut off our head.
Orhan.
My Bey.
Go to Karacahisar with your brother.
Let all Bey draw their swords.
Bring everyone to Yenişehir.
Your command, my Bey.
Bala.
You go with theAlps.
I'll go to someone and then come.
Okay, my Bey.
Come on, Alps.
Valiants.
My Allah.
Grant me the power to take revenge on the
cruels and traitors.
Amin.
Söğüt
Send word to Olof and Bayındır Bey.
Let them come to hear my new commands.
I'm going to need Olof
more than I thought.
Are you really going to give
Marmaracık to Olof?
That's what that idiot thinks.
But I will not give him any land.
When my work with Osman ends...
I'm done with Olof.
What about Osman?
What will your next move
be for him, my lady?
I will create a big hell for Osman.
A loneliness hell.
His friends and his people...
even his family...
They will not stay with him.
I will make the winds of
poverty blow on Yenişehir.
Osman Bey's people will
suffer from hunger.
And they will turn to me.
They will turn their backs on Osman.
Those who turn their backs on Osman
will be on my side.
Sultan Mother will protect Yenişehir.
İnegöl Castle
Check warehouses
so that there is no shortage.
We got in some way though.
May Allah make our end good.
Amin, my Bey.
You come uninvited.
Are you raiding our property now?
Shut up!
Get outside.
I left our calling halfway through.
They killed our Alps.
You are the only one who knew
the location of the headquarters.
She left us in the middle of the road.
I...
Do I hold you
responsible for this?
You told me this.
Like you never know me.
Even if our paths are the same.
I don't want it to
ever cross, Osman Bey.
Who is a slave to the Sultana...
Our path and his path are not the same.
You don't know what you're saying.
Are you accusing me of treason now?
You have completely
blinded your eyes.
I'm not blind or anything like that.
I know you won't tell of the
headquarters location.
But you got so small that you fell back.
They dared attack
because you weren't there.
I was leaning on you.
I considered you a mountain.
But you're not even a hill.
You hurt me the most.
What about what you did to me?
I am not a dull knife, Osman Bey.
If you sharpen me that much...
I definitely cut.
You sharpened yourself and stood before me
for kingship...
Let this be a lesson for me.
Do you know what you did?
You didn't want me.
Do you know how many I lost when
I was walking behind you?
How many wounds in my body?
How many dear people have I lost?
A few of those walking behind me
are alive.
I buried my wife and the child in her womb
in the dirt, Osman Bey.
And I buried my brothers and
comrades in the dirt.
Have we given these losses to come back
from the middle of the road for a castle?
The castle...
If the calling does not reach
its goal, all losses are in vain.
You still say castle.
Castle, what?
Don't you see, I am the ruler of Inegol.
The matter is different.
Osman.
Walk now to see if you can walk
to Köpruhisar.
Osman.
This move of ours must
have made him mad, Olof.
We broke Osman's feet.
Soon...
I will break his neck very soon.
What İsmiha Sultan wanted happened.
I think she is pleased.
What about us?
Will what we want happen?
Marmaracık has become ours.
My brother Frode is right.
What if İsmihan Sultan doesn't give
Marmaracık to us?
Olof.
İsmihan Sultan wants to meet you.
Yes, it's different.
Different.
The matter is different.
You want more.
You don't be satisfied with what you have.
Greed for possession
has blinded your heart.
Look at you.
Look at that vanity.
You are the one who brought
me to this situation.
Are you now complaining about
Turgut, whom you have made so?
Have you forgotten the injustice
you committed, Osman Bey?
I will give the castle to Öktem for sure.
Surely.
They are strangers.
If I do not give them a
property, they will leave us.
They withdraw and go.
But you...
You were my support.
I thought you were different.
But...
for a property...
I never knew you would switch sides.
I have not changed sides for
money, nor for the property.
Decide.
Choose your side.
I did not sell you.
Now come out of my castle, Osman Bey.
- Inegol
- Inegol!
It's not yours anymore.
This does not happen without blood.
I am the one who always fought.
I was always ahead.
I am the one who faced sedition.
But...
But those behind me
have always been deceived by these tricks.
I am the one who always fought.
You will fight now too.
Against me.
I give you two days to
leave this place.
We give our souls, of course.
But if you want our home...
We do not give it.
Then I take both.
There are horse tracks on both sides.
Sisters.
Open your eyes well.
Don't leave a place
without looking, come on.
We'll look everywhere, Ayşe Hatun.
May your heart be at ease.
We'll find a trace, we'll find it.
No return to Yenişehir
until a trace is found.
Where are you?
My son.
What is this?
Ülgen.
This earring belongs to Alçiçek.
If she came here...
I'm completely confused.
Did you understand any of this?
I don't know, Ülgen.
I don't know.
The only thing I know...
is that Alçiçek
caused harm to my son.
She did.
Ayşe Hatun.
Say it.
This is Aktemur's horse.
Oh my Allah, save him.
Aktemur.
Search everywhere.
Look everywhere.
Find him.
Ülgen, find my son.
We wil find him.
My daughter.
Why are you so lost?
Thinking of Aktemur again?
No.
Why would I think of the man
who left me behind and gon?
I think about what I will do.
Well done.
You listen to your mother.
That boy does not have
the courage to run away.
His love was a lie, my daughter
Listen to your mother
and don't worry about anything else, okay?
I learned my lesson, mother.
I will do what you say from now on.
So, my opinion is...
not to delay the wedding
and to have it at once.
My Bey.
What's the matter?
Are you going to the court?
Yes.
We go to the court, however...
I don't know how I will
look at Osman Bey's face.
You did nothing wrong.
A thousand people ask for a girl
and one person takes her.
There is no reason for resentment
and indignation in this.
Yes but...
it wasn't good to reject Osman Bey.
What should we do?
Why would we listen to the words of
Osman Bey in the presence of İsmihan Sultan?
You did the right thing.
It is İsmihan Sultan
who stands behind you anymore.
Alçiçek,
is she okay?
Is she satisfied?
I spoke to her.
She has consent to marry Bayındır.
Good.
Aybars.
Let's go and not be late.
Söğüt
You will wait, Beys.
Why will we wait?
Are we no longer
welcomed in the court?
Alps, what is the reason for that?
This is what Osman Bey wants.
If anyone is burdened by this...
Alps will accompany him to Yenişehir gate.
Salam Alaikum.
Alaikum Salam.
Beys.
Our meeting has become a court.
There must be a price for this, too.
And the price of this...
is to reduce our number.
Our path is more difficult than before.
But the conquests will continue.
We will continue to march
towards the enemy.
We will never bow our
necks to the oppressors.
But if someone wants to cross the
threshold of the court...
Let him consider that the noose
will be wrapped around his neck.
No one will try to cross the threshold of the court
without fearing for his head.
This is my last warning.
This is the last chance for
those who wish to return.
Those who want to go
will not be asked why.
But if someone wants to come...
Our door is always open.
He who does not risk death
does not walk this path.
Come on, Beys.
Osman Bey granted permission,
so why do you stand before us?
So?
He...
Yes.
He said those who give up are
not Bey or Alp anymore.
Whoever isn't an Alp or a Bey
had no right to carry a sword either.
He says.
If only I had smashed them with the mace.
Go ahead.
In the ninety-nine names of Allah, who
made us responsible for the conquest...
I open the court.
In the name of of Allah the Merciful.
You must have heard what
happened to our headquarters.
We heard the bad news, Osman Bey.
But the thing you
should have heard was not this.
What you had to hear was only
the good news of the conquest.
My Bey.
You keep your conquests a secret.
Who revealed the secret
of the headquarters?
I will cut off his head when I find out.
Who attacked?
It was Olof who attacked.
There is no attack or betrayal that
holds the force that can stop us.
The court was assembled
for this reason.
We will fix everything
as soon as possible.
We are ready to do
whatever it takes, my Bey.
Whether we will sacrifice blood or soul...
Thank you.
Osman Bey.
What does İsmihan Sultan
say about this situation?
You would have given me land, my Sultan.
When did your ancestors
come to Constantinople?
Two centuries ago?
Three centuries?
What makes you think
you can take the land from me...
which Rome, despite your services all
these years, did not give you so easily?
This is not the issue.
I did what you said.
Now it's your turn, Sultan.
You will give me
Marmaracık Castle.
Right now!
Sir Olof.
You are so excited to die.
I will keep my promise.
And you will never forget who I am...
Commander Olof.
Do not you dare.
If I give you the land now..
Osman will take it back from
you immediately.
Let him try.
And I will crush him under those walls.
You won't do what you want...
you will do what I want.
First, you will kill Osman.
When Osman receives the news, he will
go out to look for his nephew Aktemur.
And you will drag him
into the biggest trap.
Death trap.
Don't worry, my Sultan.
I prepared my plan a long time ago.
My Sultan, Turgut Bey is coming.
Who wonders about the opinion of
İsmihan Sultan should go with her.
Why did you enter the
threshold, Şahin Bey?
I ask to understand the
situation we will be in.
If you have any doubts, the noose is
on my neck, Osman Bey.
Thank you.
Otherwise...
What is said in the court
remains inside it.
The issue of opening Köprühisar
has been revealed.
All equipment has been destroyed.
But..
Now is the time to conquest.
They wouldn't expect us to
be ready in such a short time.
Despite their knowledge
of Köprühisar...
They will not even imagine that
we will march towards Köpruhisar.
- Alps.
- Sir.
You will cut down trees even
in the middle of the night.
You will continue to make
catapults by the light of torches.
Alps will be ready in no time.
Blacksmiths will continue to make swords.
You will finish preparations for war.
They cut our beard.
We will cut off their heads.
Inshallah, as soon as possible, my Bey
The court is over.
Get ready quickly.
The swords you will bring
are the keys to conquest.
Osman Bey.
Aktemur.
- What happened to Aktemur?
- He's not here, my Bey.
My Bey, he went to
run away with Alçiçek.
And he didn't come back.
I went to the meeting place.
His horse was there, but he was not there.
Osman Bey.
My son is not there.
What do you say, Ayşe Hatun?
Why are you doing this
without telling me?
Boran, send Cerkutay to the place mentioned
by Ayşe Hatun as soon as possible.
He should begin
searching for a trace.
Alps will get ready, we have another goal.
Your command, my Bey.
Hadrat Mother Sultan.
Mother Sultan, then let me begin
the wedding preparations at once.
Start.
Start so you can hit the road.
Walk to your destination, Bayındır.
Your command, Sultan Mother.
Yes, Turgut Bey?
What brings you here without news?
Whoever I said my brother
did not choose the truth.
On the contrary, he wants
to rule İnegöl himself.
I am here, Turgut Bey.
There is no judgment for Osman
in the place where I am.
Does he want me to take
all his possessions with one decision?
What does Osman Bey want?
Arrogance.
Too bad, you are right.
Arrogance has blinded Osman Bey's eyes.
All he wants is for this reason.
He made us behind him.
And put you in front of him.
He made many conquests.
And now he wants to rule unjustly.
Didn't you shed blood for
İnegöl, Turgut Bey?
I did.
You risked antagonizing us.
Osman fought injustice.
And now he has become one
of the oppressors.
While I'm here...
Injustice is forbidden, Turgut Bey.
If you choose my side...
Then I will give you soldiers and
swords as many as you want.
And you will always feel the presence
of the Mother Sultan behind you.
When you said this earlier, I
didn't believe you.
But I saw this
with my own eyes.
There is no place for the
unfaithful by my side.
I am on your side now, Mother Sultan.
While Othman thinks he is coming to you,
he will fall into my hands.
It will be your turn too.
But first I will kill your uncle.
And when I take what I want...
I will dedicate his blood to Odin.
You will not reach your goal, dogs.
Did you throw the bait?
First they will be confused...
We made it difficult for them to find the
traces so that they would not be suspicious.
But all traces will bring
them to the same place.
This place will be Osman's grave.
We will fight today as if
it is our last day.
And we will eliminate Osman
and those with him.
- Take care of him.
- Don't worry.
I will treat him very well.
Sharpen your axes and
let Odin be your helper.
let's go.
It's very beautiful, Marta.
Send me a roll of all these fabrics.
Absolutely, Bengi Hatun
Looking at the fabrics you have chosen,
you understand fabrics very well.
Bengi Hatun knows how to
choose the most beautiful in everything.
If you do wrong to her, you
will do wrong to us.
Give her the most beautiful
in everything she chose.
Welcome, Bayındır Bey.
Certainly.
Happily we met,
Bayıdır Bey, I have been looking for you.
We must not
delay the wedding.
Nice to say, Bengi Hatun.
I was next to the Mother Sultan.
We propose to have the
wedding tomorrow.
Especially if we have the opportunity and
all obstacles have been removed...
We must not delay it.
I will speak to Öktem Bey
and you will begin to prepare.
- Hüseyin.
- Your command, my Bey.
Send heralds everywhere.
- We have a wedding tomorrow.
- Your command, my Bey.
While you're talking
about obstacles, I don't see anyone.
What did you do to Aktemur?
I didn't do anything, however...
Apparently, someone had cleared around
before I could do anything about it.
So I didn't get my hands dirty in vain.
What I say? Allah loves this servant.
I will pay whatever Bengi Hatun chooses.
No need.
We solve our own problems.
Do what you must do, son-in-law.
What are you doing like that?
What do you smell?
Did you think it would smell like food?
Every trace has its own scent, Gürbüz.
Some traces are not seen.
Does this make sense?
Are you kidding me?
Osman Bey made me
take this lunatic next to me.
- There are people coming.
This means that you have
other skills besides eating.
Oh, if only you knew my skills...
- Salam Alaikum.
- Alaikum Salam.
Cerkutay Alp, those
traces don't lead to anywhere.
This means that we are on the right track.
All traces point to Sofular.
Continue on this path.
I will go and tell my Bey.
Give me my apple!
Come here and give me this apple!
I will burn you.. I will burn you!
Come on, Brother Gürbüz.
Anyway, I will find you.
Konur, one of Osman Bey's
Alps, wants to see you
Let him come.
What is the reason
you came here, Osman's Alp?
It is waking up from the sleep of
heedlessness after all these years, my Sultan.
I am not Osman's Alp, I was one of the
skilled leaders of the Seljuk family.
Now?
And now I am a man who
has been completely fired.
We don't accept everyone who gets fired.
Who asked you to accept me, my Sultan?
I have come here to apologize from
my country and then find what I deserve.
What treatment does he deserve, Avcı Bey?
Foot whipping forty times and
take everything he owned.
This is a mistake.
I have gone after a Bey
and have betrayed my position.
What I deserve is execution.
So, you came here to be killed
- Are you?
- Yes.
A person pays the price for his
betrayal only with his soul.
But you will pay it with our service.
I will do whatever you want, my Sultan.
Of course you will.
What is my mission?
They will think that they have demolished
and burned us, but we will not stumble.
The conquests will continue.
Whenever the call of Allah rises in our
hearts, we'll make the whole world rise up.
We will not despair.
Our goal is clear.
Our target is Köprühisar.
My Bey, our current residence is
very close to Marmaracık.
Is this out of caution?
This place will facilitate our conquests.
It is hidden and obvious at the same time.
My Bey, shall we send news to Oktem Bey,
since we are so close to Marmaragic?
Let us complete the headquarters,
then we will see.
Eyvallah my Bey.
And he will make his preparations.
We said what we have in the court.
We have nothing to hide from anyone.
And when the catapults are ready, we
will strike harder than ever.
Inshallah my Bey.
My Bey.
And what about Aktemur?
Aktemur.
My Bey.
Cerkutay.
We've found Aktemur Bey's trail.
They are keeping him in Sofular.
Are you sure?
Traces are complicated, my Bey.
However, they all refer to
the location of the Sofular.
Alps.
Get ready
We'll go get Aktemur.
My son couldn't have a joyful life.
Oh my Lord.
Lord protect my son.
My Ayse.
You will see your son, Inshallah.
Don't do this.
Right.
Osman Bey won't let those ignobles
keep Aktemur!
Of course they will come.
They will come.
Thank you.
Everyone shall know!
Tomorrow evening
in Marmaragic Castle...
Bayindir Bey and Oktem Bey's daughter
Alcicek's wedding will be held.
The whole Yenisehir is invited.
Don't do it, Alcicek!
That girl burned my son!
We do not know where my son is,
and these are holding a wedding!
Calm down, my dear Ayse.
You're all here, Hatuns.
I have come for good news.
But obviously..
...you have received the news.
We know it, Bengi Hatun.
Enjoy it.
I hope you don't regret your decision
as a mother.
I hope not, if Allah permits.
But I don't see anything I might regret.
Or are you upset that we
did not give you Alcicek?
Bengi Hatun.
Say what you're going to say quickly.
And don't keep us busy.
You're upset,
I get it.
Don't, Hatuns.
Is it a sin that Alcicek is beautiful and
her lovers are many?
1000 men desire a girl
but only one gets to marry her.
Isn't this right, Ayse Hatun?
Aktemur is not around.
Or is he ashamed to be seen?
Aktemur is a Subasi, Bengi Hatun.
He doesn't have time.
He's at duty.
Don't worry about my son.
He'll forget soon.
Of course he will forget.
He has to.
Whatever.
Send my greetings to Osman Bey.
We are all waiting for you at our wedding.
Ayse!
Ayse, calm down please.
She is playing with us!
Once I find my son...
Then I know what to do with you.
Wait for me.
I am holding back.
I can barely hold myself back.
But when that day comes....
...do not try to stop me.
Never try to stop me.
My Bey, there are soldiers
on duty on each side
And there are many of them indeed, my Bey.
We will water our swords with
the blood of infidels
We've found them.
And now we will chop off their heads.
Allah is the greatest!
Attack them,
kill them all!
Come here.
You're searching your nephew, right?
I will get what I want.
The only thing you will get today...
...is the corpse of Aktemur.
You won't see him today.
I'll get both Aktemur...
...and your soul!
Attack!
Come to me.
Come!
Cerkutay.
Baysungur.
Osman!
I came to kill you!
I came to avenge my alps!
I will kill you along with them!
Come on then!
Come!
Orhan
Praise be!
- Oh right!
Oh right!
Praise be!
- Oh Allah!
- Oh right!
Avci Bey.
What about testing Konur?
Then we can give him the duty.
Show us what you have.
You are skilled
As Avci Bey...
...you will be my bodyguard
and my assistant too.
Now go.
Can we trust him, my Sultan?
I carry out campaigns that
will destroy Osman.
He is getting destroyed.
The destroyed...
...knows that aid is here.
I am the saviour.
Turgut and Konur...
They are only the beginning, Avcı Bey.
This position you assigned him
is too close.
I keep the people I trust close to me.
I keep the people I don't trust
even closer.
Don't take your eyes off Konor.
Until we're sure he is one of us.
Your command, my sultan.
Olof!
We will not succeed!
Pull back!
- Oh Allah!
My Allah.
Today I killed one of you.
Tomorrow I will kill all of you!
Praise be upon you my valiants!
Praise be!
Sons
Come here.
Praise be!
Praise be to you!
Your hearts are as strong as your arms!
As long as you are united like this...
...no one can oppress us,
if Allah permits.
- Eyvallah my Bey.
Boran, my brother!
Nothing will hurt you!
Nothing!
Will this wound hurt you?
Are you okay brother?
Oh brother?
My Bey! Boran!
Brother!
My Bey is coming.
My Bey is coming,
you are alright brother
You are fine.
Boran.
Brother.
My Bey!
Hang on.
I'm fine, I am fine.
Come on, get ready quickly!
We will go to Yenisehir!
Come on, let's go brothers!
Let's go,
you're all right, Boran!
Come on brothers!
What a shame.
I wish the girl who stabbed you with
the dagger could see you right now.
What was her name?
Alcicek.
She is a beautiful girl.
Don't ever say her name!
Alcicek.
Osman Bey has ruined their game.
What happened, Olof?
What happened?
He did not die!
Osman Bey dealt with you.
But wait.
You will live the worst.
Wait for it.
Do not rush your death.
Your turn will come.
I swear...
I swear to Odin!
I will not die before
I drink Osman's blood.
So they couldn't hit him?
Where are they taking the goods now?
To Karaken Forest behind the castle.
They say it'll be safe there.
Good
They should guard well.
Go and check the place,
check if it's safe.
As you command my Bey.
What are they taking, Avci Bey.
What is your business
with the goods we trade?
Nothing, just curiosity.
I want to be on the
lookout and do my job.
If you want to do your job...
...don't put your nose in everything, Konur.
Let's inspect the soldiers.
Eyvallah.
Yenisehir
We have arrived, brother!
Hang on, hang on.
Lie him down here.
We arrived.
Hang on, hang on, hang on, hang on Boran!
Hang on!
Kumral Abdal!
My Bey!
Kumral Abdal, Kumral Abdal!
Come!
He lost so much blood.
Bring water and clean cloths!
Now!
Come on!
My Bey.
His wound seems deep.
My Boran!
My brother!
Press here hard, press here hard!
Boran, brother open your eyes!
Boran is fading away my Bey!
Cerkutay!
Come to your senses!
I can bear no more pain, my Bey!
I can't stand another pain, my Bey!
Nothing will happen!
Do not worry.
Boran is strong.
Nothing will happen to him.
He will open his eyes.
He will!
Boran get up!
- Cerkutay.
- My Bey!
Boran.
How do you spread the news of the
wedding without consulting me?
Talk, Bayindir!
Bengi!
Calm down.
We also see that it is early.
But Ismihan Sultan forced us to do so.
She acted, I...
I don't care about that, Bayindir!
You did not consult me!
Why are we rushing?
You have just asked for my daughter...
...and today you want to
hold the wedding as soon as possible!
My Bey, Ismihan Sultan says
that good deeds should not be postponed.
You are accusing Bayindir Bey wrongly.
How can he oppose the order of Sultan?
What is the difference between
today and tomorrow?
- They are not different, however...
- I know what you mean.
You want to put it off because your
daughter is getting married and moving out
This upsets me too.
I am her parent just like you.
How are the preparations?
Don't forget anything.
We have to send news to Osman Bey
but I am ashamed to do so!
How are we going to do that, Bayindir?
I invited them today.
But I don't know if they will come.
We did what we had to do.
It's not on us anymore.
Let Osman Bey figure out the rest.
Okay.
Why does Bengi Hatun talk like that?
I don't understand the reason
for this rush.
My mom is afraid that
I will back down.
That's why she hurries.
Are you really going to marry
Bayindir Bey?
I will marry him.
You don't love that man.
Why would you do this to yourself,
Alcicek Hatun?
What should I do, Esma?
Should I wait for the coward Aktemur
who abandoned me?
What if he didn't abandon you?
No one in the market saw him.
He vanished like a breeze.
He is probably ashamed to show up.
He must be wondering
how to look me in the eye.
Let this wedding happen,
then you'll see him around!
Komral Abdal, he has no energy.
He lost so much blood.
He will liven up once he drinks
the healing sherbet.
Our brother Boran is fighting for his life.
Turgut Bey went on one side and
Konur Alp on the other!
We are falling apart one by one, brothers.
Konur Alp is coming.
What are you doing here?
Is Boran okay?
What's your business with him? Didn't you
turn your back on your brothers?
Didn't you obey Ismihan Sultan?
Let me see my brother.
You can't see anyone.
If you have something to say...
...talk to Osman Bey.
Come on.
Preparations will continue.
The conquests will not stop
even if we have losses or ghazis.
It's not like we have just set off, my Bey.
We were born on this path.
I would sacrifice a thousand sons.
But I am sure that we will take my son
back, Insallah.
And Boran will be fine, Inshallah, my Bey.
Inshallah, he will get over this
He is my friend.
And a confidant.
We have overcome many
hardships together.
And there are still so many paths
that we will walk together
My Bey, what about Ismihan Hatun?
What is her role in this matter?
After hearing about her opposite
thoughts about the war...
...sisters stopped joining the sister union.
Her aim was to leave us alone.
Turgut.
Bayindir.
This is just the beginning.
Konur Alp was seen with Ismihan Sultan
as well.
Why didn't you count him, father?
Can I come in my Bey?
Come.
My Bey.
I don't know how he dared to come but...
...we took him to you.
Speak.
I heard where
they're holding Aktemur, my Bey.
Eyvallah.
We will continue to beat
them with our games
But we will be careful.
We will not back down from
this universal cause of ours!
Come!
Now get out of my sight!
You hit me at the first mistake
and abandon me!
- Turns out Turgut Bey was right.
- I told you to get out!
Ismihan Sultan must be willing to have you
object me.
Go and obey her.
Become her man.
You are going to learn
everything you need.
We know where Aktemur is.
Thank Allah.
But your task is not over.
Give it to me.
And you go back
to your duty, to Sogut.
Your command, my Bey.
You have to earn Ismihan Hatun's trust.
You have to learn
her every move beforehand.
My Bey, I'd like to see my brother
before I leave, if you'll excuse me
Our brothers didn't let me
as they didn't know about the game.
Can we come, my Bey?
Come.
Peace be upon you.
And may peace be upon you.
- Brother
- My Konur!
Boran.
My Bey!
We will take revenge on those who made
this to you and to Aktemur.
Inshallah my Bey.
Brother.
Forgive me.
You acted so well that I couldn't
really see the truth!
I forgive you, brother.
Thank Allah for this day, brothers!
May Allah make us stay
in this blessed path.
We got hungry huh!
You didn't eat anything
to take care of Boran, huh!
Do you see my brother Boran?
Cerkutay loves you more than he loves food
Right brother.
Look at my dear brother!
Cerkutay, you're going to make me cry.
Where is Gurbuz Alp?
Dear brothers
Not here, the food is gone, brothers!
The food is gone, brothers!
The food is gone!
Come on brother, come on!
Stop it, Gurbuz Alp, don't!
Don't!
The rest is mine, okay?
Gorbuz Alp!
I'm about to starve.
And Ulgen Hatun
doesn't even give me food.
Let me eat it.
Now put it on the ground slowly.
Brother, you know that I love bulgur
with meat very much!
Stop Stop!
Stop, stop, stop, stop!
Yes, I know!
Is that Cerkutay!
What is he saying?
I know that.
I know you love!
But actually, I am the one who loves!
Does he talk to himself?
I love!
I miss!
I want it back!
Is he talking about me?
Oh!
I...
Honestly?
Has my luck reversed?
Is Cerkutay in love with me?
Surely!
He must be getting prepared
before talking to me!
Allah!
Eh!
If I don't eat I will be angry!
I get defeated by my anger!
This is hardly enough for me!
Go away!
You finished it!
Finished!
Look at me, brother!
If you don't give it to me...
...I too will be defeated by my anger.
You took the apple from me in the morning,
do you remember?
Yes?
Now bring me an apple.
Then I'll share my food.
- Oh really?
- Apple.
An apple he wants!
Of course.
Don't move.
Apple!
Juicy apples here!
The apple, the apple!
You will pay Gurbuz Alp!
Allah reversed my luck!
He did!
Is this a dream?
We will have a double wedding!
Double wedding with Alcicek and
We can't do that
Where are you Aktemur Bey?
They will give your sweetheart to a
stranger, where are you?
My Sheik
The problems in my heart
have also filled your heart.
Have you come to heal me?
Welcome, welcome, my sheikh.
- Here.
- Eyvallah.
In the name of of Allah the Merciful,
the Compassionate.
You are afraid, Osman Bey.
I know, you're afraid.
I want to walk in the path of Hadrat Abraham
I want to destroy all those idols
with my own hands, my sheikh.
However...
However, today's idols are neither seen
with eyes nor held by the hand.
Right, Osman Bey?
Even my companion
fell into their trap!
He brags!
If he wins, he considers himself
the owner of that victory.
And now I'm afraid of not being able to
destroy those idols, my sheikh.
If this fear is in your heart...
...you should be happy, Osman Bey.
Because you can't win without it.
The moment you are victorious...
...is the moment when
you are exposed to the biggest test.
Think about it.
The first foray after the conquest of Mecca.
The Muslims won again, my sheikh.
But they were about to be defeated.
The Messenger of Allah,
when he conquered Mecca...
All victories of his
were nearly wasted.
Hunayn is a battle in which the army of the
Messenger of Allah was numerous.
They also armed themselves with
the best weapons.
They looked very strong.
But some who were among them...
...declared victory even before they fight.
They said then: "Who can beat us?"
Allah mentioned this in his book.
God Almighty said after the end of the
battle in Surat Al-Tawbah:
"In the name of of Allah the Merciful,
the Compassionate."
"Indeed Allah has given you ˹believers˺
victory on many battlefields...
...even at the Battle of Ḥunain...
...when you took pride in your great numbers,
but they proved of no advantage to you.
The earth, despite its vastness, seemed to
close in on you...
...then you turned back in retreat."
What about me?
What should I do, my sheikh?
Fear the punishment of Allah.
Do not lose your hope
about His mercy, Osman Bey.
The son of Adam is very forgetful.
You and your amry shall not forget...
The few have triumphed over the many
many times.
Remember the Battle of Badr, in which the
Muslims were few in number.
Remember the Battle of Hunayn, in which
Muslims outnumbered the enemy, Osman Bey.
Osman Bey.
Do not forget.
Who won the Battle of Badr
is the faith of the believers...
....and their obedience
to Allah Almighty.
As for Huneyn, despite all that power...
...because of a moment of inattention
and a moment of arrogance...
...they were about to be defeated.
And now we are going
through the same exam.
We are being tested with our selfs,
my sheik.
Humans are there to be tested, Osman Bey.
That's for sure.
Know that whenever Muslims
hold on to the rope of Allah...
...they will always win.
The ones who obey their desires
will suffer.
It is true what you say, Sheikh.
Osman Bey, without looking for the truth...
...considers us responsible
for the attack on the headquarters.
Moreover...
He asks for Ingol,
where we gave many martyrs.
But I will not give it to him.
I won't give him the only land I rule!
What shall we do, my Bey?
Will raise our swords to our brothers?
We will do what we have to do.
Whoever wants to leave can leave now!
There is the door!
You show leavers the door.
What will you show to the one
who is entering, Turgut Bey?
Your anger?
Kumral Abdal.
No.
Sit down, Turgut Bey.
All these conflicts happened
because you wanted to sit there.
So sit down now.
If you get up, you'll hurt me.
Your reproach proves that...
What hurts you is me going after
what's my right!
I still want to answer your question.
All these fights and conflicts
are not because of my love of the throne!
Rather, because of the injustice
of Osman Bey.
I did not come here to gossip about
Osman Bey, Turgut...
...Bey.
When the dress of love is taken off...
...a man is covered in selfishness.
I can never find the
dress of selfishness to fit you
You are on the wrong side.
I came to say this.
My Kumral Abdal is mistaken!
Neither money nor position
is more important than my case!
I entered this path in order to
spread the name of Allah Almighty!
I will always walk this way!
Is this why you divided the community
because of a position issue, Turgut?
The property I have acquired is the mark
of my case!
And it's halal, and you know that!
Why would I be ashamed?
Your tongue and your heart
doens't talk the same way, Turgut.
If you go to war like this.
If an arrow hits you.
You will die, Turgut.
The Turgut I knew before
wouldn't die!
Because lovers do not die!
But you die, Turgut!
You are oblivious.
Wake up from the sleep of inattention!
Wear the clothes of love!
The oblivious die!
Lovers never die, Turgut!
Yenisehir
Alps!
Come on, get ready, we're going out!
My Bey, my Bey.
Allow us, my Bey, let us come too.
It's hard to sit here with
my hands crossed
Ayse Hatun, don't blame me.
We did this without your knowledge.
But Aktemur, my nephew,
is entrusted to me.
I'll take him and bring back to you
safe and sound. Don't worry.
Insha'Allah.
May Allah make your path easy.
Eyvallah.
Alps!
Ride!
You will continue to distribute them to
merchants, Beys and everyone, Avci Bey.
Let people know where the gold
is coming from.
And let the merchants know
with whom they will trade.
Do your job well, Avci.
Give gold to whomever wants gold.
Give horses to whomever wants a horse.
Give sword to whomever wants a sword.
After your order, the incoming immigrants
have been placed in near tribes, my Sultan.
The seeds of hypocrisy were spread among
the beys of Karacahisar.
Nice.
This will help us a lot later.
Has the news reached Olof?
Yes my Sultan.
Aktemur's head will fall on Yenisehir
like a fire.
Didn't your uncle, your Osman Bey
come to rescue you?
You have been captured because of love.
And he let you govern the city.
For this reason, Osman deserves nothing.
Ignoble dog!
You underestimate us.
That girl, Alcicek, for whom you
were captured.
Do you know where she is now?
I told you not to say her name.
At the wedding.
It means that you are not that valuable.
Do you really expect me to believe that?
What a pity.
Too bad.
While you are slowly dying here...
...she is getting married.
I'll take you from Osman first.
You will be the first
to be separated from him
Do you want to say goodbye?
Will he die that early?
I was going to skin him.
I will now send you to hell!
I bear witness that there is no God but Allah,
and I bear witness that Muhammad is His Messenger
Uncle!
Hell is only for people like you!
Osman!
Eric
Come on.
Never do this.
Don't do this Osman!
You will say the same
when my sword is on your neck!
But I won't back down then either!
No.
No!
Aktemur.
Aktemur, Aktemur!
You are fine, right?
Hold on, hold on.
Alps, help!
Come on, we will go to Yenisehir.
- Boran
- My Bey.
Our destination will be different.
Hear me carefully.
Constantinople
Palace of the Emperor
Who stopped the army
that I sent to help Commander Olof?
Which of you?
Sir.
- Emperor Andronicus...
- It's you!
You are the one who stopped them.
Tell me.
Where is Andronicus?
Absent.
Who is in his place?
I am.
You no longer serve the Byzantine state.
In order to prove your loyalty towards me...
...I command you to kill this traitor.
Immediately.
Who knows for
how long you have been friends?
You killed him without asking
a single question
without even objecting!
can I trust you?
Yes sir.
Nice.
All armies are under your command.
I'd like you to send one of
your best units to Olof at once.
Marcus!
Yes sir.
Bring all the agreements
that Andronikos made with Osman.
Immediately.
Yes sir.
Yes, Mr. Olof
You didn't pay the necessary attention.
You couldn't handle a single Subasi!
We gave you a mission!
You failed miserably!
Well, we didn't say anything!
We've already made Subasi
worse than dead!
Until he gets on his feet...
...I'll take my Hatun
and start a living in my tent.
Now that you had a wedding,
why did you come here?
It is the order of Ismihan Sultani.
She was very angry that you
missed Subasi.
I calmed her down.
Right now...
Until news comes from the Mother Sultan...
...you will never move a single movement.
I came to say this.
As long as she gives me what I want...
...I will do what Ismihan Sultan says.
Go tell her this.
Hussein!
Good, let's go now.
Groom shall not keep
the bride waiting.
Come on.
My heart burns whenever
I see you like this.
Why do you torture yourself, Alcicek Hatun?
I thought I had my back
on a mountain that wouldn't fall.
That mountain fell.
I was crushed under it.
I died, Esma.
Let it happen, whatever it is.
Get up, get up now!
Run away!
Don't do this to yourself.
I am okay with my destiny Esma.
Don't be sad anymore.
My beautiful daughter
You are very pretty.
Not a single tear shall fall from
those beautiful eyes of yours any more.
Whatever you did, I
did it for your own good.
Do not forget this.
This way, my Bey
please enter
We got what we wanted, right, Hussein?
Yes my Bey.
Praise be! Praise be!
Has there been anything
I couldn't get when I wanted?
My Sultan.
We are glad you came.
Greetings, Bayindir.
Masha Allah, everyone is here.
Where is Osman Bey?
We have sent him news.
But I don't know if he will come.
My Sultan.
Is this reasonable?
The huge Bey.
Is he leaving his two important Beys alone
on this remarkable day?
You see that, right, Beys?
Not everyone deserves to be statesmen
If you are a Bey, you should
put your personal matters aside.
In fact, you know Osman much
better than we do, Turgut Bey.
You supported him for years.
He erased you
with his arrogance.
It's not important for you if he joins
our wedding or not.
Osman Bey is coming.
Peace be open you.
And may peace be upon you.
What is it?
Weren't you expecting us?
Welcome my Bey.
We didn't know you would come.
But you acted maturely.
May Allah bless you.
Where is our bride?
She is coming now, Malhun Hatun.
Okay then.
Let's sit here.
Malhun, come on.
Allah bless my daughter
My Alcicek.
Your fate is as beautiful as your face.
Osman Bey has come, Bengi Hatun.
So you came Osman.
I will check them.
Come on.
Alcicek, praise be!
We are leaving.
Bala Hatun, where are we going?
What is going on here?
Hurry up, we'll take you to Aktemur.
Aktemur, the one who left me?
Ah! I will shout now!
Girl, that man faced death for you!
While Aktemur was on his way to you,
the enemy captured him.
He is now unconscious.
Are you saying the truth, Bala Hatun?
- But...
- There is no but.
Alcicek, you are not interested
in this marriage.
I know you just have to.
But as long as we are in this country...
...no one will be forced into marriage.
Your mother will come now, girl, come on!
I know from day one that you like Actimore
, right?
If you say it still is, so be it
- Is it true what you say?
- Yes
No, we're kidding
God forgive us
It's true what we say girl, come on
- Come on!
- Who accompanies Osman Bey?
- Malhun Hatun and his alps.
Is Bala Hatun not there?
Where is she?
If Bala Hatun is not with him...
This means that Osman
did not come to congratulate.
They will kidnap Alcicek!
Run!
Tell the alps!
Close the doors immediately!
Come on.
Open the door.
Break it.
Don't do this, Alcicek.
Don't do this to us.
Don't, my daughter.
Alcicek!
The passage that will lead us out
is here, Bala Hatun.
Let's hurry.
Good.
Ulgen, you inform Osman Bey.
Come on.
Come on, Alcicek.
Did you think that we would
turn our backs on you...
...because we could not take the girl,
Ismihan Sultan?
You surprise me very much, Osman Bey.
No.
Don't ever be surprised.
You haven't seen anything yet.
I see that...
...my presence disturbs you a lot.
And you're looking at me curiously
about what I'm going to say.
I hope you haven't done anything wrong.
What is wrong for you is right for us.
You will not be able to
pay for your actions.
There is none among you
who can make me pay any price.
Your tricks, betrayals and sedition cannot
make us lose anything from our hearts!
Neither love nor patriotism!
Oktem Bey!
They have kidnapped Alcicek!
Alcicek and Aktemur are
going to marry tomorrow.
Soldiers!
Alps.
In Inegol Castle, where Gunduz Bey
watered the land with his blood.
We invite you all to our wedding.
Please contact turkision@gmail.com for any inquiries